# Leszek\* Pietrzak

\*Spelling: try "lesheck";-)

Birthday: January 21st, 1987

Current location: Warsaw, Poland

Nationality: Polish

**Phone**: +48692569704

E-mail: <a href="mailto:smutnyleszek@gmail.com">smutnyleszek@gmail.com</a>

Website: <a href="http://github.com/smutnyleszek">http://github.com/smutnyleszek</a>

The three values closest to my heart are: order, meaning and simplicity.

I am a creator, I always loved building something new: be it through writing, drawing or coding. As for frontend development, I love that my work can be experienced live in the browser and that I can publish anything in just a few minutes.

As I fear for the future of humanity, I don't want to throw more senseless evil out there - I would love to take part in a meaningful, nature- and future-friendly projects.

#### Skills

I have strong frontend development skills with some backend experience. I can do identity design, UI design and illustration - I mainly use Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign. I am no stranger to Scrum, Kanban, recruitment, introducing new people into projects and copywriting.

I'm familiar with all the OSs, but my favourite setup is MacOS with Atom.

Technologies I would love to work with: JS (vanilla or ES6 Babel), Angular, React, NPM, cssnext and Jekyll.

Some technologies I worked with: HTML (Twig), CSS (Compass, Sass, cssnext, BEM, MADCSS), JavaScript (CoffeeScript, ES6 Babel, Angular, React, Alt, Backbone, Phaser, Lodash, jQuery, TweenMax), TDD (Karma, Jasmine, PhantomJS), Grunt, NPM, Git, CEF, Jekyll, MySQL, PHP (Symfony2), Jira, Asana.

## **Employment**

November 2014 - Present

Frontend Engineer @ GOG.com - Warsaw, Poland - gog.com/galaxy

My main responsibility was creating a frontend of GOG Galaxy desktop application. I also develop some webapps and take part in recruiting new developers and introducing them to the project. During work here I took part in launching GOG Galaxy and creating The Witcher 3 game.

Technologies: ES6, Angular, Lodash, TDD (Karma, Jasmine, PhantomJS), Twig, Sass, BEM, MADCSS, CoffeeScript, Grunt, NPM, Git, CEF, Jira, Asana

#### March 2007 - Present

Illustrator, Designer & Web Developer @ Self-employment - Worldwide - leszekpietrzak.com

I'm always open for small design and web jobs to give me opportunity to do something crazy and try something new. I also work on some open-source projects and tools on my spare time. Some cool web projects are:

- Hues color converter tool (React, Alt, ES6, RequireJS, Karma, cssnext, MADCSS)
- Akabusk simple OMDb movie finder (Angular, ES6, Karma, cssnext, MADCSS)
- Mad Skeleton CSS boilerplate (Jekyll, Node, cssnext, MADCSS)
- <u>HashTabber</u> hashchange-driven tabbed content switcher (ES5, Compass)

#### June 2013 - November 2014

Web Designer & Frontend Developer @ Clos Brothers - Warsaw, Poland - closbrothers.pl

I was working in a small team delivering websites and webapps for big clients (Toyota) and smaller, educational ones, too (Museum of the History of Polish Jews, Silesian Risings Museum).

Technologies: Angular, Phaser, jQuery, TweenMax, Compass, Jekyll, Twig, Symfony2, PHP, Grunt, Git, SVN.

October 2012 - July 2013

Graphic Designer & Web Developer @ Trewebs - Warsaw, Poland - trewebs.com

In this semi-startup, I was hired to design the UI and identity for diet app. As time went on, there were less design tasks and a need for developer arisen - as I was already familiar with HTML and CSS, I started to learn and work on some small web development projects.

Technologies: jQuery, Compass, Drupal, WordPress, PHP, MySQL

### Education

### September 2010 - September 2013

Graphic Design @ Wyższa Szkoła Nauk Humanistycznych i Dziennikarstwa - Poznań, Poland

Licentiate degree (BA) with highest score (5)

### September 2007 - September 2010

Cultural Studies @ Wyższa Szkoła Nauk Humanistycznych i Dziennikarstwa - Poznań, Poland

## September 2006 - September 2007

Computer Science @ Adam Mickiewicz University - Poznań, Poland

# Language skills

- Polish native
- English professional
- German basics
- Toki Pona basics

### **Interests**

Evolution of life, existential philosophy, traditional tattoo, ambient music, fantastic literature, American B-movies, Haiku, contemporary art and European comics.